codility.com 2019-05-06

# Data Privacy Notice - Codility

**I have sent my CV to Codility or I am being considered for recruitment by Codility.**

  1. **Who we are**

We at Codility are the Data Controller of information we use for recruitment and selection where you have supplied us with your CV or other personal data; we are the Data Processor of information that has been supplied to us indirectly such as via an employment agency or service. We can be contacted at +44 (208) 970 78 68 or [jobs@codility.com](mailto:jobs@codility.com).

  2. **a) We have received your CV/personal data from you directly**

If your personal data held by Codility has been supplied by you for recruitment purposes then we are the Data Controller of your personal data.  It will be processed under our Legitimate Interests of selecting and recruiting the most suitable candidates to join us at Codility.  Your details, including your CV, will be processed by us for the purpose of supporting our recruitment and selection processes. They will be held by us for 12 months after which they will be anonymised and used for statistical analysis of our own recruitment and selection processes. Any remaining personal data will be deleted at this time.  **or**

  2. **b) We have received your CV/personal data from you indirectly**

If we have received your CV or personal data from a third party (such as a Recruitment Agency or online service) then we will be the Data Processor of your personal data and obliged to act in line with the instructions that we are given by the Data Controller (to whom you may have provided your CV previously).  You will have given your Consent to the Data Controller or your data is being processed and shared under another, GDPR compliant Legal Basis such as their Legitimate Interests or the Performance of a Contract with you.

These instructions will be laid down by the Data Controller and include the following details:

  * the subject matter and duration of the processing;
  * the nature and purpose of the processing;
  * the type of personal data and categories of data subject; and
  * the obligations and rights of the controller.

The agreement between the third party (the controller) and Codility will include the following terms:

That Codility must:

  * only act on the written instructions of the controller (unless required by law to act without such instructions);
  * ensure that people processing the data are subject to a duty of confidence;
  * take appropriate measures to ensure the security of processing;
  * only engage a sub-processor with the prior consent of the third party and a written contract;
  * assist the third party in providing subject access and allowing data subjects to exercise their rights under the GDPR;
  * assist the third party in meeting its GDPR obligations in relation to the security of processing, the notification of personal data breaches and data protection impact assessments;
  * delete or return all personal data to the third party as requested at the end of the contract; and
  * submit to audits and inspections, provide the third party with whatever information it needs to ensure that they are both meeting their Article 28 obligations, and tell the controller immediately if it is asked to do something infringing the GDPR or other data protection law of the EU or a member state.

  3. **Rights that you have**

As your personal data is held by Codility you have rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (the GDPR) that Codility fully support. Your rights are:

  * The right to request a copy of your personal data which Codility holds about you;
  * The right to request that Codility corrects any personal data if it is found to be inaccurate or out of date;
  * The right to request your personal data is erased where it is no longer necessary for Codility to retain such data;
  * The right to withdraw any consent you have given to the processing of your data, at any time;
  * The right to request that Codility provide the data subject with his/her personal data and where possible, to transmit that data directly to another data controller, (known as the right to data portability) for the performance of a contract with the data subject and in either case the data controller processes the data by automated means.
  * The right, where there is a dispute in relation to the accuracy or processing of your personal data, to request a restriction is placed on further processing;
  * The right to object to the processing of personal data including for marketing purposes
  * The right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioners Office (the ICO).

These rights are more fully explained at <https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/>

Should you have any questions regarding these rights and how Codility supports them, please contact us at [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com).

  4. **New Purpose**

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, not covered by this Notice, then we will provide you with a new Notice explaining this new use prior to commencing the processing and setting out the relevant purposes and processing conditions. Where and whenever necessary, we will seek your prior consent to the new processing.  Prior to deletion Codility anonymises data received from Candidates for the purpose of statistical analysis relating to the recruitment process.  Such anonymised data is no longer considered to be personal data and is not within the scope of the GDPR.

  5. **Sharing Data**

Codility will not share your data with any companies outside of the Codility Group (other than those that are involved in our recruitment and selection processes) without your explicit Consent. 

  6. **Updating your Data**

If you wish to request to update or change the information that we use of yours or how we use it, you can do so by contacting us by emailing [jobs@codility.com](mailto:jobs@codility.com). 

Please ensure you notify us of any updates, amendments and corrections to your information by contacting us via the means above.

  7. **Contacting Us**

Any queries or comments about this privacy notice or for requests relating to the rights listed above, please contact Codility at [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com).

If you wish to make a complaint about how we use your information, please contact us in the first instance via [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com) and we will do our best to help.

If you are still unhappy, you can contact the Information Commissioner’s Office via their website ([www.ico.org.uk](http://www.ico.org.uk%20/)). 

We will occasionally update this privacy notice and our [privacy policy](https://app.codility.com/privacy-policy/).  We encourage you to periodically review this notice to be informed of how we use your information.

This Privacy Notice was last updated November 2018.

More information regarding Codility and our Data Protection Policy can be found at [www.codility.com](https://www.codility.com/)

Back to the top

**I have an account with Codility’s Programmers’ Home service**

  1. **Who we are**

We at Codility are the Data Controller of personal data that is supplied to us when individuals sign-up for our Programmers’ service.

We can be contacted at +44 (208) 970 78 68 or [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com).

  2. **We received your personal data when you signed-up for our Programmer’s service**

Your personal data held by Codility has been supplied by you for the purpose of managing and supporting your Programmer’s Account and its usage.  We are the Data Controller of your personal data.  It will be processed under our Legitimate Interests of providing you with the described service, to authenticate you and address you in communication about the service. Your personal data (including your IP address) will be held by us for 12 months after your account is terminated at which time it will be deleted.

  3. **Rights that you have**

As your personal data is held by Codility you have rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) that Codility fully support. Your rights are:

  * The right to request a copy of your personal data which Codility holds about you;
  * The right to request that Codility corrects any personal data if it is found to be inaccurate or out of date;
  * The right to request your personal data is erased where it is no longer necessary for Codility to retain such data;
  * The right to withdraw any consent you have given to the processing of your data, at any time;
  * The right to request that Codility provide the data subject with his/her personal data and where possible, to transmit that data directly to another data controller, (known as the right to data portability) for the performance of a contract with the data subject and in either case the data controller processes the data by automated means.
  * The right, where there is a dispute in relation to the accuracy or processing of your personal data, to request a restriction is placed on further processing;
  * The right to object to the processing of personal data including for marketing purposes
  * The right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioners Office (the ICO).

These rights are more fully explained at <https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/>

Should you have any questions regarding these rights and how Codility supports them, please contact us at [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com).

  4. **New Purpose**

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, not covered by this Notice, then we will provide you with a new Notice explaining this new use prior to commencing the processing and setting out the relevant purposes and processing conditions. Where and whenever necessary, we will seek your prior consent to the new processing. 

  5. **Sharing Data**

Codility will not share your data with any companies outside of the Codility Group without your explicit Consent.

  6. **Updating your Data**

If you wish to request to update or change the information that we use of yours or how we use it, you can do so by contacting us by emailing us at [support@codility.com](mailto:support@codility.com)

Please ensure you notify us of any updates, amendments and corrections to your information by contacting us via the means above.

  7. **Contacting Us**

Any queries or comments about this privacy notice or for requests relating to the rights listed above, please contact Codility at [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com).

If you wish to make a complaint about how we use your information, please contact us in the first instance via [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com) and we will do our best to help.

If you are still unhappy, you can contact the Information Commissioner’s Office via their website ([www.ico.org.uk](http://www.ico.org.uk/)).

We will occasionally update this privacy notice and our [privacy policy](https://app.codility.com/privacy-policy/).  We encourage you to periodically review this notice to be informed of how we use your information.

This Privacy Notice was last updated November 2018.

More information regarding Codility and our Data Protection Policy can be found at [www.codility.com](https://www.codility.com/). 

Back to the top

**I have visited Codility’s website and / or have completed an enquiry form**

  1. **Who we are**

We at Codility are the Data Controller of personal data that we collect through our website or through other media.

We can be contacted at +44 (208) 970 78 68 or [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com). 

  2. **We received your personal data when completed a web form on our website**

Your personal data collected by Codility has been supplied by you for the purpose of managing and supporting your enquiry or your request for information about our services.  We are the Data Controller of your personal data.  It will be processed under our Legitimate Interests of providing you with information so that we may continue to grow our business. Your details will be held by us for 6 months after we have a final, verifiable contact with you at which time they will be deleted. 

  3. **Rights that you have**

As your personal data is held by Codility you have rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) that Codility fully support. Your rights are:

  * The right to request a copy of your personal data which Codility holds about you;
  * The right to request that Codility corrects any personal data if it is found to be inaccurate or out of date;
  * The right to request your personal data is erased where it is no longer necessary for Codility to retain such data;
  * The right to withdraw any consent you have given to the processing of your data, at any time;
  * The right to request that Codility provide the data subject with his/her personal data and where possible, to transmit that data directly to another data controller, (known as the right to data portability) for the performance of a contract with the data subject and in either case the data controller processes the data by automated means.
  * The right, where there is a dispute in relation to the accuracy or processing of your personal data, to request a restriction is placed on further processing;
  * The right to object to the processing of personal data including for marketing purposes
  * The right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioners Office (the ICO).

These rights are more fully explained at <https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/>

Should you have any questions regarding these rights and how Codility supports them, please contact us at [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com).

  4. **New Purpose**

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, not covered by this Notice, then we will provide you with a new Notice explaining this new use prior to commencing the processing and setting out the relevant purposes and processing conditions. Where and whenever necessary, we will seek your prior consent to the new processing.

  5. **Sharing Data**

Codility will not share your data with any companies outside of the Codility Group without your explicit Consent.

  6. **Updating your Data**

If you wish to request to update or change the information that we use of yours or how we use it, you can do so by contacting us by emailing us at [support@codility.com](mailto:support@codility.com).

Please ensure you notify us of any updates, amendments and corrections to your information by contacting us via the means above.

  7. **Contacting Us**

Any queries or comments about this privacy notice or for requests relating to the rights listed above, please contact Codility at [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com).

If you wish to make a complaint about how we use your information, please contact us in the first instance via [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com) and we will do our best to help.

If you are still unhappy, you can contact the Information Commissioner’s Office via their website ([www.ico.org.uk](http://www.ico.org.uk/)).

We will occasionally update this privacy notice and our [privacy policy](https://app.codility.com/privacy-policy/).  We encourage you to periodically review this notice to be informed of how we use your information.

This Privacy Notice was last updated November 2018.

More information regarding Codility and our Data Protection Policy can be found at [www.codility.com](https://www.codility.com/). 

Back to the top

**I have a corporate account and am Customer of Codility’s services**

  1. **Who we are**

We at Codility are the Data Controller of personal data that is supplied to us when individuals sign-up for our Programmers’ service.

We can be contacted at +44 (208) 970 78 68 or [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com).

  2. **We received your personal data when you signed-up as a Customer of Codility**

Your personal data held by Codility has been supplied by you for the purpose of managing and supporting your account with us: to authenticate you; to address you in communication about the service and your activity on our site; updating you about our services and/or industry related news.  We are the Data Controller of your personal data.  It will be processed under the Performance of the Contract that we have with your organisation to supply the described service. Your personal data (including your IP address) will be held by us for 36 months after the contract is terminated at which time they will be deleted.

  3. **Rights that you have**

As your personal data is held by Codility you have rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (the GDPR) that Codility fully support. Your rights are:

  * The right to request a copy of your personal data which Codility holds about you;
  * The right to request that Codility corrects any personal data if it is found to be inaccurate or out of date;
  * The right to request your personal data is erased where it is no longer necessary for Codility to retain such data;
  * The right to withdraw any consent you have given to the processing of your data, at any time;
  * The right to request that Codility provide the data subject with his/her personal data and where possible, to transmit that data directly to another data controller, (known as the right to data portability) for the performance of a contract with the data subject and in either case the data controller processes the data by automated means.
  * The right, where there is a dispute in relation to the accuracy or processing of your personal data, to request a restriction is placed on further processing;
  * The right to object to the processing of personal data including for marketing purposes
  * The right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioners Office (the ICO).

These rights are more fully explained at <https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/>

Should you have any questions regarding these rights and how Codility supports them, please contact us at [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com).

  4. **New Purpose**

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, not covered by this Notice, then we will provide you with a new Notice explaining this new use prior to commencing the processing and setting out the relevant purposes and processing conditions. Where and whenever necessary, we will seek your prior consent to the new processing.

  5. **Sharing Data**

Codility will not share your data with any companies outside of the Codility Group without your explicit Consent.

  6. **Updating your Data**

If you wish to request to update or change the information that we use of yours or how we use it, you can do so by contacting us by emailing us at [support@codility.com](mailto:support@codility.com)

Please ensure you notify us of any updates, amendments and corrections to your information by contacting us via the means above.

  7. **Contacting Us**

Any queries or comments about this privacy notice or for requests relating to the rights listed above, please contact Codility at [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com).

If you wish to make a complaint about how we use your information, please contact us in the first instance via [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com) and we will do our best to help.

If you are still unhappy, you can contact the Information Commissioner’s Office via their website ([www.ico.org.uk](http://www.ico.org.uk/)).

We will occasionally update this privacy notice and our [privacy policy](https://app.codility.com/privacy-policy/).  We encourage you to periodically review this notice to be informed of how we use your information.

This Privacy Notice was last updated November 2018.

More information regarding Codility and our Data Protection Policy can be found at www.codility.com.

Back to the top

**I have received or requested information regarding Codility’s services**  

  1. **Who we are**

We at Codility are the Data Controller of personal data that is supplied to us when individuals sign-up for our Programmers’ service.

We can be contacted at +44 (208) 970 78 68 or [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com).

  3. **We process your personal data to provide you with information about our services**

Your personal data is held by Codility for the purpose of supplying you with information about the products and services that Codility supply.  We are the Data Controller of your personal data.  It will be processed under our Legitimate Interests of marketing to businesses and business people in our industry so that we may continue to grow user base. As mentioned below, you have the right to object to our use of these Legitimate Interests in relation to your data. Should you invoke this right we will cease to contact you immediately and delete your data from our systems.  Otherwise your personal data will be held and used by us for 12 months after our last verifiable contact with you after which time it will be deleted.

  4. **Rights that you have**

As your personal data is held by Codility you have rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (the GDPR) that Codility fully support. Your rights are:

  * The right to request a copy of your personal data which Codility holds about you;
  * The right to request that Codility corrects any personal data if it is found to be inaccurate or out of date;
  * The right to request your personal data is erased where it is no longer necessary for Codility to retain such data;
  * The right to withdraw any consent you have given to the processing of your data, at any time;
  * The right to request that Codility provide the data subject with his/her personal data and where possible, to transmit that data directly to another data controller, (known as the right to data portability) for the performance of a contract with the data subject and in either case the data controller processes the data by automated means.
  * The right, where there is a dispute in relation to the accuracy or processing of your personal data, to request a restriction is placed on further processing;
  * The right to object to the processing of personal data including for marketing purposes
  * The right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioners Office (the ICO).

These rights are more fully explained at <https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/>

Should you have any questions regarding these rights and how Codility supports them, please contact us at [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com).

  5. **New Purpose**

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, not covered by this Notice, then we will provide you with a new Notice explaining this new use prior to commencing the processing and setting out the relevant purposes and processing conditions. Where and whenever necessary, we will seek your prior consent to the new processing.

  6. **Sharing Data**

Codility will not share your data with any companies outside of the Codility Group without your explicit Consent.

  7. **Updating your Data**

If you wish to request to update or change the information that we use of yours or how we use it, you can do so by contacting us by emailing us at [support@codility.com](mailto:support@codility.com).

Please ensure you notify us of any updates, amendments and corrections to your information by contacting us via the means above.

  8. **Contacting Us**

Any queries or comments about this privacy notice or for requests relating to the rights listed above, please contact Codility at [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com).

If you wish to make a complaint about how we use your information, please contact us in the first instance via [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com) and we will do our best to help.

If you are still unhappy, you can contact the Information Commissioner’s Office via their website ([www.ico.org.uk](http://www.ico.org.uk/))

We will occasionally update this privacy notice and our [privacy policy](https://app.codility.com/privacy-policy/).  We encourage you to periodically review this notice to be informed of how we use your information.

This Privacy Notice was last updated November 2018.

More information regarding Codility and our Data Protection Policy can be found at www.codility.com.

Back to the top

**I have a trial account with Codility**

  1. **Who we are**

We at Codility are the Data Controller of personal data that is supplied to us when organisations sign-up for a trial of one of our services.

We can be contacted at +44 (208) 970 78 68 or [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com).

  2. **We received your personal data when you signed-up for a trial with Codility**

Your personal data held by Codility has been supplied by you for the purpose of managing and supporting your trial account with us: to authenticate you; to address you in communication about the service and your activity on our site; updating you about our services and/or industry related news.  We are the Data Controller of your personal data.  It will be processed under our Legitimate Interests of allowing organisations to use and assess our services as part of our sales process so that we may continue to grow our business. Your personal data (including your IP address) will be held by us for 12 months after the trial is terminated at which time they will be deleted. 

  3. **Rights that you have**

As your personal data is held by Codility you have rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (the GDPR) that Codility fully support. Your rights are:

  * The right to request a copy of your personal data which Codility holds about you;
  * The right to request that Codility corrects any personal data if it is found to be inaccurate or out of date;
  * The right to request your personal data is erased where it is no longer necessary for Codility to retain such data;
  * The right to withdraw any consent you have given to the processing of your data, at any time;
  * The right to request that Codility provide the data subject with his/her personal data and where possible, to transmit that data directly to another data controller, (known as the right to data portability) for the performance of a contract with the data subject and in either case the data controller processes the data by automated means.
  * The right, where there is a dispute in relation to the accuracy or processing of your personal data, to request a restriction is placed on further processing;
  * The right to object to the processing of personal data including for marketing purposes
  * The right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioners Office (the ICO).

These rights are more fully explained at <https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/>

Should you have any questions regarding these rights and how Codility supports them, please contact us at DPO@codility.com. 

  4. **New Purpose**

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, not covered by this Notice, then we will provide you with a new Notice explaining this new use prior to commencing the processing and setting out the relevant purposes and processing conditions. Where and whenever necessary, we will seek your prior consent to the new processing. 

  5. **Sharing Data**

Codility will not share your data with any companies outside of the Codility Group without your explicit Consent.

  6. **Updating your Data**

If you wish to request to update or change the information that we use of yours or how we use it, you can do so by contacting us by emailing us at [support@codility.com](mailto:support@codility.com).

Please ensure you notify us of any updates, amendments and corrections to your information by contacting us via the means above.

  7. **Contacting Us**

Any queries or comments about this privacy notice or for requests relating to the rights listed above, please contact Codility at [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com).

If you wish to make a complaint about how we use your information, please contact us in the first instance via [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com) and we will do our best to help.

If you are still unhappy, you can contact the Information Commissioner’s Office via their website ([www.ico.org.uk](http://www.ico.org.uk/)). 

We will occasionally update this privacy notice and our [privacy policy](https://app.codility.com/privacy-policy/).  We encourage you to periodically review this notice to be informed of how we use your information.

This Privacy Notice was last updated November 2018.

More information regarding Codility and our Data Protection Policy can be found at www.codility.com.

Back to the top

**I have taken part in an interview or assessment that used the CodeLive service**

  1. **Who we are**

We at Codility are the Data Processor of personal data that is supplied to us when individuals join a CodeLive session.

We can be contacted at +44 (208) 970 78 68 or [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com).

  2. **We received your personal data so you could be invited to a CodeLive session**

We received your personal data from a third party (such as a Recruiter) and we are the Data Processor of your personal data.  We are obliged to act in line with the instructions that we are given by the Data Controller (to whom you may have provided your personal data previously). You will have given your Consent to the Data Controller or your data is being processed and shared under another, GDPR compliant Legal Basis such as their Legitimate Interests or the Performance of a Contract with you.

These instructions will be laid down by the Data Controller and include the following details:

  * the subject matter and duration of the processing;
  * the nature and purpose of the processing;
  * the type of personal data and categories of data subject; and
  * the obligations and rights of the controller.

The agreement between the third party (the controller) and Codility include the following terms:

That Codility must:

  * only act on the written instructions of the controller (unless required by law to act without such instructions);
  * ensure that people processing the data are subject to a duty of confidence;
  * take appropriate measures to ensure the security of processing;
  * only engage a sub-processor with the prior consent of the third party and a written contract;
  * assist the third party in providing subject access and allowing data subjects to exercise their rights under the GDPR;
  * assist the third party in meeting its GDPR obligations in relation to the security of processing, the notification of personal data breaches and data protection impact assessments;
  * delete or return all personal data to the third party as requested at the end of the contract; and
  * submit to audits and inspections, provide the third party with whatever information it needs to ensure that they are both meeting their Article 28 obligations, and tell the controller immediately if it is asked to do something infringing the GDPR or other data protection law of the EU or a member state.

  3. **Rights that you have**

As your personal data is held by Codility you have rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (the GDPR) that Codility fully support. Your rights are:

  * The right to request a copy of your personal data which Codility holds about you;
  * The right to request that Codility corrects any personal data if it is found to be inaccurate or out of date;
  * The right to request your personal data is erased where it is no longer necessary for Codility to retain such data;
  * The right to withdraw any consent you have given to the processing of your data, at any time;
  * The right to request that Codility provide the data subject with his/her personal data and where possible, to transmit that data directly to another data controller, (known as the right to data portability) for the performance of a contract with the data subject and in either case the data controller processes the data by automated means.
  * The right, where there is a dispute in relation to the accuracy or processing of your personal data, to request a restriction is placed on further processing;
  * The right to object to the processing of personal data including for marketing purposes
  * The right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioners Office (the ICO).

These rights are more fully explained at <https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/>

Should you have any questions regarding these rights and how Codility supports them, please contact us at [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com).

  4. **New Purpose**

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, not covered by this Notice, then we will provide you with a new Notice explaining this new use prior to commencing the processing and setting out the relevant purposes and processing conditions. Where and whenever necessary, we will seek your prior consent to the new processing.

  5. **Sharing Data**

Codility will not share your data with any companies outside of the Codility Group without your explicit Consent.

  6. **Updating your Data**

If you wish to request to update or change the information that we use of yours or how we use it, you can do so by contacting us by emailing us at [support@codility.com](mailto:support@codility.com)

Please ensure you notify us of any updates, amendments and corrections to your information by contacting us via the means above.

  7. **Contacting Us**

Any queries or comments about this privacy notice or for requests relating to the rights listed above, please contact Codility at [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com).

If you wish to make a complaint about how we use your information, please contact us in the first instance via [dpo@codility.com](mailto:dpo@codility.com) and we will do our best to help.

If you are still unhappy, you can contact the Information Commissioner’s Office via their website ([www.ico.org.uk](http://www.ico.org.uk/)).

We will occasionally update this privacy notice and our [privacy policy](https://app.codility.com/privacy-policy/).  We encourage you to periodically review this notice to be informed of how we use your information.

This Privacy Notice was last updated November 2018.

More information regarding Codility and our Data Protection Policy can be found at www.codility.com.

Back to the top
